

+1 (778) 855-6870 sbagga@sfu.ca sandybagga.com

SKILLS

Experience Design
UX/UI Design
Interaction Design
Visual Design
Prototyping
Brand Strategy
User Testing

TOOLS

Adobe CC

Figma

Sketch

ProtoPie

Keynote

VS Code

Pen + Paper

INTERESTS

Jazz-Fusion Music Shred Guitar Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu World Religions Stand-Up Comedy Mindfulness Video Games

SOCIAL





sandybagga95

Sandy Bagga

An experience designer building meaningful narratives

I'm a senior design student based in Vancouver, BC. I'm interested in brand strategy, user journeys, and product design. I think interactions with an ecosystem of apps, products, and services can and should be analysed from a narrative perspective.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Experience Designer — Intern

IBM Canada Lab / Sep 2019 - present

Designing a system for IBMers to collaborate with senior undergrads and local community initiatives

Organized IBM's live presence at CASCON × EVOKE promoting academic-entrepreneurial relationships

Redesigning methodologies for government-public relations in a community-based research project

UX/UI Designer — Intern

Clearly.ca / Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Gained a new understanding of customers in the direct-to-customer e-commerce landscape

Worked closely with the front-end development team to design a web experience for premium brands

Measured the results of the design's deployment with customer experience and analytics teams

UX/UI Designer — Intern

Visier Inc. / Jan 2017 - Aug 2017

Designed and delivered a critical user experience during a transition to a new visual design language Generated visual elements (icons, toasts, etc.) in Illustrator for the reimagined design styleguide Implemented an atomized approach to UI design in Sketch that streamlined developer handoff

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Composer

Live from the Olive Garden / 2019

I am part of a group called 'Live from the Olive Garden' and our eponymous debut EP is available online. The album as part of a course project, and its positive reception led us to continue writing as a group.

Learning Support Worker

Amazing Tutors Children's Foundation / Feb 2019 - Jun 2019

Gaining deep understanding of student needs to ensure that the best possible support is delivered Building and maintaining relationships with students, making a genuine investment in their success

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Science / Spring 2021School of Interactive Arts + Technology

Berklee College of Music

Guitar Sessions / Summer 2013
Berklee Summer Programs